Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXI is arranged in 367 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXI. ORGANIZATION
  - Sub-Series 230-0. Organization
    - General-Organization Committees of Lodges No. 505-997, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - General-Organization Committees of Lodges No. 2-499, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - General, 1931 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - General, 1930-1931 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - General, 1930 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - General, 1929 (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
    - General, 1929 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1929-June 1929.
    - Committees. Lodges No. 745 to 6252, 1943 (Box 75a, Folder 1)
    - General Organization Committees-Lodges No. 1 to 300 Inclusive, 1941 (Box 75b, Folder 1)
    - General, Non-member lists, 1929 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Committees. Lodges No. 1 to 742, 1943 (Box 75a, Folder 2)
    - General Organization Committee-Lodges No. 301-600 Inclusive, 1941 (Box 75b, Folder 2)
    - General, 1929 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      Nov. 1929-Dec. 1929.
    - General (Regional Meeting, Field Forces), 1943 (Box 75a, Folder 3)
      Jan.-Aug. 1943.
    - General Organization Committee-Lodges No. 601-900 Inclusive, 1941 (Box 75b, Folder 3)
    - General, 1929 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      Nov. 1929-July 1929.
    - Numerical List of Lodges (also name and location), 1943 (Box 75a, Folder 4)
    - General Organization Committee-Lodges No. 1201-1650 Inclusive, 1941 (Box 75b, Folder 4)
    - General, 1928 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      Nov. 1928-Aug. 1928.
    - General, 1942 (Box 75a, Folder 5)
      July-Dec. 1942.
    - General Organization Committee-Lodges No. 2001-2325 Inclusive (Express), 1941 (Box 75b, Folder 5)
    - General, 1927 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - General, 1942 (Box 75a, Folder 6)
      Jan.-June 1942.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 75b, Folder 6)
      Nov. 1949-March 1950.
    - General, 1926 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - General, 1941 (Box 75a, Folder 7)
      Oct.-Dec. 1941.
    - General, 1949 (Box 75b, Folder 7)
      Aug. 19, 1949-Oct. 1949.
    - General, 1925 (Box 75, Folder 8-9)
    - General, 1949 (Box 75b, Folder 8)
      March 1949-Aug. 18, 1949.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 75b, Folder 9)
      1948-Feb. 1949.
    - General, 1925-1927 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 75b, Folder 10)
    - General, 1924 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - 230-0(B). General-Articles For Bulletin, 1938-1946 (Box 75b, Folder 11)
    - General, 1923 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Committees. Lodge No. 1 to Lodge No. 6317, 1946 (Box 75b, Folder 12)
    - General, 1922 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - General, 1945 (Box 75b, Folder 13)
    - Changes. Chairmen Organization Committees, 1945 (Box 75b, Folder 14)
    - Sante Fe, 1921-1934 (Box 75b, Folder 15)
      1921-March 1934.
    - Committees. Lodge No. 951 to 2325, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Committees. Lodges No. 1 to 950, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Committees. Lodges No. 3 to 910 Inclusive, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Committees. Lodges No. 911 to 6275 Inclusive, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - General (Small Properties), 1950-1959 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      1950-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - General, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - General, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      Nov. 1950-51.
    - General, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      April 1950-Oct. 1950.
  - Sub-Series 230-1. Organization
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1945-1953 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1942-1944 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1921-1941 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-2. Organization
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1941-1943 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1933-1940 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1923-1929 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-3. Organization
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1941-1950 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1938-1940 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1933-1937 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1925-1934 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-4. Organization
    - Delaware & Hudson Railroad, 1941-1949 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Delaware & Hudson Railroad (D. & H.), 1934-1940 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Delaware & Hudson Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-5. Organization
    - Charleston & Western Carolina (C. & W. C.), 1933-1948 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-8. Organization
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western, 1944-1953 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-9. Organization
    - Louisiana & Arkansas, 1933-1954 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-10. Organization
    - 230-10(b). Detroit, Toledo & Ironton (D. T. & I.)-former Grand Lodge Organizer (G. L. O.), Baldwin's file, 1920-1939 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      1920-21 and 1937-39.
  - Sub-Series 230-11. Organization
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad, 1923-1927 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-12. Organization
    - Michigan Central, 1944-1953 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Michigan Central Railway, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1943-1944 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      Nov. 1943-March 31, 1944.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1943 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1943-Oct. 1943.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      April 1942-Dec. 1942.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1941-1942 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      July 1941-March 1942.
  - Sub-Series 230-13. Organization
    - Central of Georgia Railway, 1941-1943 (Box 79a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-14. Organization
    - Louisville & Nashville, 1952-1953 (Box 79a, Folder 6)
      Sept. 26, 1952-53.
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1946-1952 (Box 79a, Folder 7)
      April 1946-July 1952.
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1952 (Box 79a, Folder 8)
      Aug. 1952-Sept. 25, 1952.
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1944-1946 (Box 79a, Folder 9)
      March 1944-March 1946.
  - Sub-Series 230-15. Organization
    - Santa Fe, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Santa Fe, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Santa Fe, 1955-1956 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Santa Fe, 1950-1954 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Santa Fe, 1947-1949 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      Nov. 1945-Dec. 1946.
    - Sante Fe, 1944-1945 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      March 1944-Oct. 1945.
  - Sub-Series 230-17. Organization
    - Railway Express Agency, 1941 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1941-June 1941.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      July 1940-Dec. 1940.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1940-June 1940.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      July 1939-Dec. 1939.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1939-June 1939.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1937-1938 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1929-1936 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1921-1928 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1952-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      July 1952-June 1954.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      April 17, 1952-June 1952.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1949-1952 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      May 1949-April 16, 1952.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1947-1949 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      July 1947-April 1949.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      Aug. 1946-June 1947.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      April 1946-July 1946.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1945-1946 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      Oct. 1945-March 1946.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      Jan. 1945-Sept. 1945.
    - Railway Express Agency, 1944 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      April 1944-Dec. 1944.
  - Sub-Series 230-18. Organization
    - Santa Fe, 1943-1944 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      1943-Feb. 29, 1944.
    - Santa Fe, 1942 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Santa Fe, 1941 (Box 79a, Folder 14)
    - Santa Fe, 1940 (Box 80a, Folder 1)
    - Santa Fe, 1939 (Box 80a, Folder 2)
    - Santa Fe, 1938 (Box 80a, Folder 3)
    - Santa Fe, 1938 (Box 80a, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1938-July 1938.
    - Santa Fe, 1936-1937 (Box 80a, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe, 1935 (Box 80a, Folder 6)
      Sept. 1935-Dec. 1935.
    - Santa Fe-Chronological history of representation dispute on the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway System Lines, 1934 (Box 80a, Folder 7)
    - Santa Fe, 1935 (Box 80a, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1935-Aug. 1935.
    - Santa Fe, 1934 (Box 80a, Folder 9)
      July 1934-Dec. 1934.
    - Santa Fe, 1934 (Box 80a, Folder 10)
      April 1934-June 1934.
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific System, 1944-1949 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      March 1, 1944-1949.
  - Sub-Series 230-19. Organization
    - Union Pacific-Lines West, 1945-1956 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - 230-19(b). Union Pacific-Lines West, 1941-1944 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Union Pacific-Lines East, 1944-1956 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - 230-19(a). Union Pacific-Lines East, 1941-1943 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis (C. C. C. & St. L.), 1921-1942 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 230-20. Organization
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1950-1956 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      Aug. 1950-56.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1948-1950 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      May 1948-July 1950.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1946-1947 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      May 1946-Aug. 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1946 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1946-April 1946.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1947-1948 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      Sept. 1947-April 1948.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1944-1945 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      April 1944-45.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      1943-March 31, 1944.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      June 1942-Dec. 1942.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1942-May 1942.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - New York, Chicago & St. Louis (N. Y. C. & St. L.)-Nickel Plate, 1921-1942 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-21. Organization
    - 230-21(a). Great Northern, 1942-1944 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - 230-21(B). Great Northern, Lodge No. 593, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1933-1945 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway (St. L. S. W.), 1921-1942 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-23. Organization
    - Texas & Pacific Railway, 1941-1954 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Texas & Pacific, 1933-1940 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-24. Organization
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie (M. St. P. & S. S. M.)-Soo Line, 1945-1950 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-25. Organization
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1937 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Names and Address of Secretaries of Lodges at Pennsylvania Connecting Points of Lodges Holding Penn. Membership of General Chairmen of Connecting Lines, 1937 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (special), 1936 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 230-25(3). Pennsylvania Railroad, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 230-25(2). Pennsylvania Railroad, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 230-25(1). Pennsylvania Railroad, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1936-March 17, 1936.
    - 230-25(1). Pennsylvania Railroad, 1935 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      Jan. 1, 1935-Aug. 10, 1935.
    - 230-25(2). Pennsylvania Railroad, 1935 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      Aug. 12, 1935-Dec. 30, 1935.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      Dec. 30, 1933-July 27, 1934.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1938 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1934 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      July 27, 1934-Nov. 30, 1934.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1934 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      Dec. 1, 1934-Dec. 21, 1934.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1933 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1932 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1931 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1921-1929 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway (M. K. & T.), 1945-1954 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway (M. K. & T.), 1941-1944 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-26. Organization
    - Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway (M. K. & T.), 1933-1940 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway, 1921-1930 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1948-1956 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1945 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      Aug. 22, 1945-Dec. 1945.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1945 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      June 12, 1945-Aug. 21, 1945.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.)-Miscellaneous information and historical background, company union activities, N. C. & St. L. Clerks Association, etc., 1934-1945 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1943-1945 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      Sept. 30, 1943-June 11, 1945.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1942-1943 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      June 1, 1942-Sept. 29, 1943.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1946-1947 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1942 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      March 6, 1942-May 29, 1942.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1941-1942 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      Nov. 1, 1941-March 5, 1942.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1924 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      Dec. 9, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 230-27. Organization
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway (St. L. S. W.), 1943-1953 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-28. Organization
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1944-1954 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      March 1, 1944-54.
  - Sub-Series 230-29. Organization
    - Western Pacific, 1935-1953 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Reading Railway System, Philadelphia and Reading, 1938-1940 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Reading Railway System, Philadelphia and Reading, 1933-1937 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Reading Railway System, Philadelphia and Reading, 1920-1931 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-31. Organization
    - Baltimore & Ohio, 1946-1950 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      May 1946-50.
    - Baltimore & Ohio, 1944-1946 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1944-April 1946.
  - Sub-Series 230-32. Organization
    - The Alton Railroad, 1938-1946 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Bessemer & Lake Erie, 1933-1940 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-33. Organization
    - Wheeling & Lake Erie Railway, 1941-1946 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-34. Organization
    - Pere Marquette Railway, 1941-1955 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-35. Organization
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific System, 1942-1944 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      1942-Feb. 29, 1944.
    - Southern Pacific, 1940-1941 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines, 1933-1939 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines, 1931 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines, 1921-1929 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway (Frisco), 1941-1946 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-36. Organization
    - Kansas City Terminal Company, 1941-1953 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      1941-June 22, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 230-37. Organization
    - Union Depot-Columbus, Ohio, 1948-1953 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-38. Organization
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1942-1944 (Box 79a, Folder 10)
      1942-Feb. 23, 1944.
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1940-1941 (Box 79a, Folder 11)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1932-1939 (Box 79a, Folder 12)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1921-1930 (Box 79a, Folder 13)
    - 230-38(a). New York Central Lines West, 1944-1947 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      March 1, 1944-1947.
    - 230-38(b). New York Central (East), 1944-1946 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - 230-38(b). New York Central (East), 1942-1943 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-39. Organization
    - Alabama, Tennessee & Northern, 1933-1949 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-40. Organization
    - Southern Pacific Company-Texas & Louisiana, 1950-1956 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Texas and New Orleans (T. & N. O.), 1941-1949 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railway, 1921-1924 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-41. Organization
    - Boston & Albany Railroad, 1944-1951 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Boston & Albany Railroad, 1935-1943 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-42. Organization
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway, 1936-1953 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Oregon-Washington Railroad & Navigation Company, 1921-1933 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-43. Organization
    - Spokane, Portland & Seattle Railway, 1936-1953 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-44. Organization
    - Boston & Maine, 1935-1940 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Boston and Maine, 1921-1933 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-45. Organization
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad, 1937-1947 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Southern Railway, 1941 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Southern Railway, 1940 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Southern Railway, 1933-1939 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Southern Railway, 1921-1932 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-46. Organization
    - Southern Pacific Lines in Texas and Louisiana, Texas & New Orleans Railroad Company, 1933-1940 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Southern Pacific, Texas and Louisiana Lines, 1921-1931 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-47. Organization
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha (C. St. P. M. & O.), 1935-1953 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (C. M. St. P. & P.), 1941-1944 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      1941-Feb. 28, 1944.
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, 1921-1931 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific (C. M. ST. P. & P.) Railroad, 1935-1940 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 230-48. Organization
    - Norfolk and Southern Railroad, 1935-1956 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk and Southern Railroad, 1925-1930 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-49. Organization
    - Erie Railroad, 1941-1942 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Erie Railroad, 1938-1940 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Erie Railroad, 1935-1937 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Erie Railroad, 1934 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Erie Railroad, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Erie Railroad, 1930-1932 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Erie Railroad, 1927-1929 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Erie Railroad, 1921-1926 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-50. Organization
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway (Frisco), 1921-1932 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway (St.L.S.F) (Frisco), 1933-1940 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-51. Organization
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad, 1939-1946 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-52. Organization
    - St. Paul Union Depot, 1933-1953 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1933-1940 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1930 (Box 98, Folder 15)
      Jan. 16, 1930.
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1921-1922 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-53. Organization
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1952-1953 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis (M. & St. L.), 1933-1950 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-54. Organization
    - Western Maryland, 1933-1939 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Western Maryland Railroad, 1921-1929 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-55. Organization
    - Missouri and Arkansas Railway Company (Mo. & Ark. Rwy. Co.), 1937-1946 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-56. Organization
    - Wheeling & Lake Erie Railway (W. & L. E. Ry.), 1933-1940 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Wheeling & Lake Erie Railway, 1921-1931 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-57. Organization
    - Michigan Central, 1934-1940 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Michigan Central, 1921-1930 (Box 79a, Folder 1)
    - Chicago and North Western Railway, 1944-1955 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Chicago and North Western (C. & N. W.) Railway, 1941-1943 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-58. Organization
    - Union Pacific-West, 1938-1940 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Union Pacific Lines (East), 1938-1940 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1934-1937 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1931 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1932-1933 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-59. Organization
    - Washington Terminal Company, 1941-1953 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-60. Organization
    - Pere Marquette Railway, 1933-1940 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Pere Marquette Railway, 1921-1931 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville (C. I. & L.), 1935-1952 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-61. Organization
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad (B. & L. E.), 1941-1952 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Steamship Clerks, General, 1933-1940 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - 230-61(5). Steamship Clerks, Pacific Coast, 1933-1937 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Steamship Clerks, 1921-1929 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-62. Organization
    - Erie Railroad, 1944-1945 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      March 1944-45.
    - Erie Railroad, 1943-1944 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      1943-Feb. 1944.
  - Sub-Series 230-63. Organization
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1941 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1941-Oct. 1941.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L. Ry.), 1935-1940 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway (N. C. & St. L.), 1921-1934 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-64. Organization
    - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic (D. S. S. & A.), 1933-1954 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Burlington, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1923-1929 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 230-65. Organization
    - Belt Railway of Chicago, 1940-1953 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-66. Organization
    - Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (P. & L. E.), 1923-1943 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      1923 and 1933-43.
  - Sub-Series 230-67. Organization
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western (D. L. & W.), 1938-1940 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western (D. L. & W.), 1933-1937 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western, 1921-1931 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad (C. B. & Q. R. R.), 1944-1945 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      Jan. 1944-45.
  - Sub-Series 230-69. Organization
    - Southern Railway, 1944-1947 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      March 1, 1944-47.
    - Southern Railway, 1942-1944 (Box 93, Folder 15)